{
    "id": "35834ad2c46c4062acf225d1b404b66c",
    "title": "Do or Make",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Has he agreed to ………………….. the work?",
            "description": "Do can mean execute or carry out.",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "make",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c6bc7d84896a483d97050d386dd48273"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ……………………….. what I told you?",
            "description": "Do can mean finish or complete.",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "done",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3b7b40df2eea418988b36132e9795bd3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The company …………………….. bicycles and tricycles.",
            "description": "To make is to produce or manufacture.",
            "answers": [
                "makes",
                "does",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "137215b8718c43d29ea71fb31670c9ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you always ………………………. trouble?",
            "description": "We say make trouble. ",
            "answers": [
                "making",
                "doing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "50a7fcc7fda645dab8ad74a8a7bb4d1f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Will this tablecloth ……………………. or should I use another?",
            "description": "Do can mean suffice or be good enough.",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "make",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e16ab8a7221e48ea9f10678c1614f91e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………. a speech on the occasion.",
            "description": "To make a speech is to deliver a speech.",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "did",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7c5224a7dd1045ce9456d6168499d942"
        },
        {
            "question": "They …………………… the kitchen and the bathrooms every day.",
            "description": "To do the kitchen is to clean it.",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "make",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b948b49fbc2d47b799720964e486330d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I won’t go and you can’t ……………………… me.",
            "description": "To make someone go is to compel them to go.",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "done",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f4c404cdbefe4961b128f3eb1ea7bfa5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Laws are …………………… to be obeyed.",
            "description": "To make laws is to enact them.",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "did",
                "done"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5dcffd6bbd964894b49188556d010e3b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Last summer we ……………………. ten countries in one month.",
            "description": "To do ten countries is to travel through ten countries.",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "done",
                "made"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c19d98498e0d404b8020cd6da355edc7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hurry or we won’t …………………… the train.",
            "description": "To make the train is to catch it.",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "done",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "22d7bacc682a428a9081753ee0835555"
        },
        {
            "question": "When buying a bag, look closely at its ....................................",
            "description": "Make can mean brand.",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "make",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "310d54e4d9d54d9ab624251af10a7b29"
        }
    ]
}